everyone this is Catherine welcome
Catherine
sitting next to Catherine is her best
friend Angelica welcome Angelica
I see a little over two years ago
Catherine gave birth to a beautiful baby
boy and she named him Manuel
two weeks later Angelica gave birth to a
beautiful baby girl and she named her
Alicia
these two women have more than just the
friendship in common these two children
might have the same father a man named
escort not my kids none
so
here's the problem Escada denies both of
these kids both of them
more than 19 years old and despite what
these crazy are saying I got no
kids Catherine and I have always had an
on and off relationship every time you
break up she goes and sleep with other
guys first time I seen Captain's baby I
took one look at it and said it was too
chunky and walked out she even put
another dude's name on the birth
certificate that alone tells me I'm not
the father a Helicon and I only messed
around a couple of times that was
nothing but a booty call when she told
me she was pregnant I had to change my
number because I was tired of her
blowing out my phone I just think
Catherine and Helga can't get enough of
me that's the only reason they want me
to be a father I got a better chance of
getting struck by lightning to be the
father of these kids
thank you
no no you already know and I just like
him both of those kids are good and you
know it nope
[Applause]
do these kids think of themselves as
brother and sisters
[Applause]
but slept
you told us gardo you were pregnant what
did he say he was just like are you
serious because we were broken up so he
thought I was trying to get him back
ain't nobody want to be with him okay
okay you want me to go with you last
night
[Applause]
and Angelica uh when you were pregnant
and you told him what did he say about
that he said that I was lying and I was
just the one I stand like he said
because
so what happened when you all were kind
of having a problem and he would walk
and you know break up a little bit he
would go back with both of us at the
same time
gotta do what you gotta do these kids
are two weeks apart
yes that means he was having sex with me
and her at the same time because they're
two weeks
everything
that one was with me when I had Mike
I wasn't there no
no no no
for two weeks after here he is everybody
Welcome him
[Applause]
there we go
[Music]
sit down sit down here let me let me see
these kids you don't think you look like
them look at them look at them yep look
at the kid
[Applause]
yeah
just tell me that's not your kid
and don't mean damn
never mind yeah serious escardo yeah
okay we find out today huh why don't you
think they're they're your kids
thought you had what sleeping with two
people right that makes me a sweat you
guys
[Applause]
if you're the father of these kids
you're gonna take care of these kids
[Applause]
oh my God
please sit down thank you settle this
right now okay
all right so Angelica we're gonna do you
first right okay we're gonna find out
about that beautiful little girly here
sorry
when it comes to two-year-old Alicia
escardo you are not
[Applause]
beautiful she's my kid and my kid I
don't care and my kids
when it comes to two-year-old Manuel
escardo you are not
[Applause]
oh
God
[Applause]
[Music]
you don't want to be around them they
don't want to be around you
okay
both both of you we'll be glad to help
you you want us to give somebody a DNA
test we'll be glad to all right
everyone this is Ashley welcome Ashley
to the show
to see Ashley's 19. yes and she came
here desperate to clear her name she's
being accused by her boyfriend Brad of
being a cheater so much so that Brad now
denies their one-year-old son Bradley
Ashley says the person fueling this fire
is none other than Brad's meddling
mother Karen who's sitting in our own
Ashley says she's tired of Brad being a
mama's boy she's fed up with his
mother's attempts to ruin her
I am sick is tired of trying to prove to
my boyfriend Bradley and his mother
Karen that my son Bradley is his son
I made one mistake of cheating on Brad
when I was 13 years old and he just
won't let it go
Brad needs to stop acting like a mama's
boy and realize that this is his kid he
looks just like him and ask for Karen
she's nothing but a redneck hillbilly if
she needs to mind her own damn business
are you trying to tell me that you and
Brad would not be here except for her
yes
[Applause]
there's a bean with him Karen are you
brainwashing your son no I am not you're
not huh
[Applause]
what do you think
she's a cheating
[Applause]
it's supposed to be we wouldn't be here
he'd rather be
[Applause]
when you were 13 years old yes I made a
mistake of cheating on him well first of
all you shouldn't be having sex at 30.
yes I shouldn't have mine I knew
but it's none of her business she knew
me and herself were together yeah we
were laying down it I was laying down at
the age of 13 but it was with him I made
the mistake of cheating on him he knew
this that was the last time I cheated on
him here's Brad come on out here
[Applause]
we're gonna get a chair for you okay all
right all right we're gonna get Brad you
think it's your mother who's brainwashed
you or do you know
[Applause]
what to do next door everybody
sleep with somebody
we're gonna find out right now okay
you were asked during your relationship
with Brad have you had sex with one of
his family members that you're all
worried about yeah you said no the lie
detector determined you're telling the
truth
[Applause]
you don't want to do that you don't want
to do that
your ass during your relationship with
Brad have you had sex with any men from
your neighborhood
you admitted to our lie detector
administrator you have done so more
determined it was three times
[Applause]
during your relationship have you had
sex with one of Brad's friends you
admitted to our lie detector
administrator you have done so more than
one time
[Applause]
you were asked
do you have doubts that Bradley is
Brad's son you said no the lie detector
determined that was a lie
[Applause]
but the proof wait a second do you want
to be the father of this child yeah I do
I treat him like my doors
foreign
Bradley Brad you are the father
so you want to make a family out of it
despite what's going on you want to make
a family out of it Karen Bud out
everyone this is Kayla welcome Kayla
finally means everything to Kayla she
has devoted six years of her life to
this man Kenneth they have two they have
two children together
now sadly Kayla fears her very own
cousin Angelique has been having an
affair with him
guess what Angelique is also known
around the country as a former teen
guest on the Mari show
I mean you think that your cousin is
making it with your guy yes I am and she
ain't only been on this show for once
she's been on the show more than one
time Maury she been on this show she has
sex with dudes for double cheeseburgers
with bacon Marty
but you have to be that was way back
she's growing up now
I mean that was like four years ago it
don't mean nothing worried I don't mean
nothing okay but but you gotta have do
you have evidence that they're doing it
together dude Marty yeah he fell asleep
on her hip talking about they was drunk
would you find under the pillow I found
some earrings you know the bigger the
hoop the bigger the HootSuite
no no no
have you thrown him out of the house no
but if he fell he gonna get through out
the house today Marty I know that Marie
he gonna be gone today because guess
what
we asked him about everybody all right
now Kenneth and Angelique have taken a
lie detector test we're going to get the
results later but first this is what
Kenneth had to say to the producers
Kaylee and I got a great relationship I
never felt this way in my life about no
woman before I wouldn't do anything to
hurt her or what we got going on her
family means the world to me without
them there is no me angelique's just my
friend we're just buddies honestly she's
not even my type we went out for a few
drinks maybe I had one too many so I
fell asleep next to Angelique but it
doesn't mean that I'm out cheating candy
keeps pushing me away with all these
accusations she needs to stop
everybody here's Kenneth welcome Kenneth
[Applause]
relationship stop no stop nothing stop
nothing stop nothing sit down sit down
Canon
how you doing more you love her I love
her with all my no you don't you don't
love nothing you don't you have nothing
you don't laugh nothing
you would not humiliate her by being
with her cousin Maury I would never do
such a thing I love her with all my
heart
[Music]
share your picture how about those two
little kids
gross
I mean he's a good daddy isn't he yeah
he's a good daddy but a bad man now you
listen to me all of these accusations
[Applause]
okay
I'm about to welcome back somebody been
here twice before Angelique this is what
she said my path is my path I am a
changed woman I will never hurt Kayla by
Sleeping with her man I have learned by
my mistakes I respect myself and I
respect my body most of all I respect my
cousin relationship with Kenneth these
accusations are tearing our family apart
Caleb barely speaks to me she won't even
look at me and it's our children who are
suffering the most Kenneth is Shady but
it ain't with me when a man doesn't come
home at night you know something's up
Kayla I miss you and I love you I just
want things to go back to the way they
were
here's Angelique
Angelique see you in a long time good to
see you first of all first of all have a
seat
something like that if I did something
wrong when I take a lot of taxes
[Applause]
wait wait a second okay what you and
Kenneth have been caught doing meaning
like sleeping on the floor that's all
you were doing no we're gonna don't get
this straight today honey I laid on the
floor she was on the couch and Kenneth
came up over to me and laid next to me
on my on my hip and I said Kenneth he
was already knocked out okay you know
what I mean I got up and I went to next
how about the bathroom nothing I think
I lied about that honey nothing ever
happened in the bathroom I don't know
where that came from okay
we asked you were the hoop earrings and
the white t-shirt that Kayla found did
they come from when you were having sex
with another woman you said no the lie
detector determined you're telling the
truth
they asked you did you have sex with any
other women whose texts that Kayla found
in your phone you said no the lie
detector determined that was a lie
we asked you Kayla wait a second you got
to hear this these are important
questions we asked you when you come
home smelling like cheap perfume was it
because you were having sex with another
woman you said no the lie detector
determined that was a lie
[Applause]
I said no the lie detector determined
that was a lie thank you
[Applause]
got sex with Angelique when Kayla found
you together in the bathroom you said no
the lie detector determined you're
telling the truth
have you ever had any attack of any kind
with Kayla's cousin Angelique you said
no the lie detector determined you're
telling the truth
[Applause]
why why
go get out of my face I'm done with you
I'm done with you
get out of my face get out of my face
everyone out there who is a parent
everyone out there who's a teen
please pay attention to this segment
because this is what happens when teens
play adult games
everyone please welcome to the show 14
year old unique
and welcome unique's mother Ileana
as I said unique is 14. she is a
straight A student
she wants to be a pediatrician
a year ago in this young life unique
discovers she's pregnant
and if that wasn't painful enough unique
had to tell her boyfriend Richard
and her mother
that she also had sex with another guy
so unique is unsure if Richard or the
other boy is the father of her now
four-month-old daughter Athena watch I'm
14 years old I'm in the 8th grade and I
have a daughter named Athena who's only
four months old I'm an honorable student
and I had dreams of being a pediatrician
one day when I got pregnant at 13 I feel
like my dreams were gone
I know that this is another boy that
could be Athena's Dad I'm hoping for
Richard to be Athena's father I wake up
I have to get my baby ready and change
her diaper and put her back to sleep
when I come home from school I have to
give her baths give her love because
she's a baby and she's in need for that
my mom always taught me that if I'm
grown enough to have sex then I'm grown
enough to take care of the
responsibility
try to teach my daughter about sex and I
did the best I could
I never thought I'd be a Grandma's
before the age of 30. never even if Rich
is not the father I'm still going to be
there I don't think any baby she has a
baby
I want you to know about Richard who's
15.
because with the help of his family he
has vowed to help unique take care of
baby
thank you
I know this is about you I know it's
about Athena I know it's about you as a
young mother
but it's also about a lot of teens isn't
it yeah because they don't realize what
they're doing until the mistake happens
were you surprised when you found out
you were pregnant yeah because I never
thought I would be pregnant at a young
age like I would talk about people being
pregnant at a young age and it backfired
on me I got pregnant at a young age not
only that Ileana you were pregnant at a
young age I try to help break the cycle
I told her about it
I told her all about it how hard it has
been how old were you when you were
pregnant I was 14. I gave birth at 15. I
didn't have my mom I didn't have nobody
I did it alone
and you swore and you swore to yourself
you wouldn't let your daughter do it
alone
I wasn't going to let the cycle continue
I was going to be there every step of
the way
you know what uh unique you can still be
a doctor you know
do you think Athena favors Richard his
sister his sister his nose and
everything oh
oh
so cute
[Applause]
the reason you're here is there's a
possibility it might not be yes
and by the way the other guy you have no
idea where he is do you no well first of
all we're going to clear this up one way
or another today
[Applause]
and I'm anxious to meet Richard this is
what Richard had to say watch I never
thought I'd be in the situation at such
a young age I'm 15 years old and I might
be the father of unique's daughter
Athena a unique told me she was pregnant
I was shocked but I know there's a
chance that I might be the baby father
so I'm a man up and do what I have to do
I'm not afraid of being a young dad
because I have a very supportive family
to back me up I'm not here to support me
today
no matter what happens I'm really hoping
that I'm proving to be a Venus father
but if she's not mine I will still be
there for you
here's Richard
you're hoping at the age of 15 that this
child is yours yes
wow
because I really love unique and
I know
nothing
all right I've waited long enough let's
hope for the best
[Applause]
when it comes to four-month-old Athena
Richard
you are not
now
we're at your disposal Ileana will do
anything you want to do if you want us
to help find the other guy we will
uh
Richard I don't know what your thoughts
are I mean you're probably devastated
it's okay
but I think you're mature enough
with a lot of thought and a lot of help
and by the way my counselor will be
there with you
to make the decision it's right for you
okay all right and you need to be there
for you
everyone this is Cherokee welcome
Cherokee to the show
Cherokee Cherokee 17 years old when she
was 16 she found out she was pregnant
with her now nine-month-old son Jonathan
now at the time Cherokee was terrified
to tell the boy named Austin that she
was pregnant he was 14.
so as usual everyone when we talk about
teenage pregnancies
this is serious
every year around 750 000 teenagers in
the United States will get pregnant and
Cherokee became part of that statistic I
was just 16 years
I found out that I was pregnant I was
terrified to tell Austin and his family
so I kept it a secret I told him only
two months before I gave birth
for Cherokee and Austin their friendship
had been along and it was a devastating
loss that brought these two teens to
this dramatic point
Austin because he
Brother John
[Music]
John and it was Austin who was there to
help me it was around the time that I
became pregnant
Austin then just 14 years old was a high
school football player with his whole
life ahead of it I rumors out of school
that Cherokee might be pregnant I was
too scared to even tell my mom
Austin is my baby and he's a total
mama's boy I was angry knowing that they
had sex at such a young age
more than two-thirds of teenagers who
have a baby will not graduate from high
school Austin began to deny that he was
Jonathan's father I felt like my heart
was ripped out of my chest so I dropped
out of school sometimes I want to be
Jonathan's father but sometimes I don't
baby Jonathan is a lot of fun so if he
is my son I am going to do the right
thing I love baby Jonathan as he was my
own but my baby also needs to live his
life
these are babies having babies you hit
it from Austin
and you hid it from his mother
then he hid it from his mother longer
than you hid it from him was Austin
there the day you gave birth yeah he
wasn't in the room with me but he was at
the hospital he got to hold him he was
one of the first people in there when I
got to see Jonathan
did he help you with Jonathan he was
there for the first three and a half
months and then
[Applause]
and then
but
and then school started back up in oh
school started he started denying that
he was Jonathan's dad why he got back
around his friends rumors got started
[Applause]
how do you get along with his mother
good they are really close you know what
she told my producers she wants her son
to have a nice life that every teenager
should have but she also loves
your little boy
Cara Austin and his mom charity why
don't we welcome them here they are
oh okay
can I tell you something Austin
you look young
yeah
that's your child
possibility
I don't want to go on any further with
this I want
to find out one way or another you all
deserve that there's no reason drawing
this out anymore
I assume charity that your family will
be involved in Jonathan's life if no
matter what no matter what
hello
I am heartbroken I hate that every once
in a while that he'll be yours and then
you deny him and then you'll you tell
people he's yours and then you tell
people he's not
I hate that you can go when you can hang
out with your friends all the time and
I'm
I'm I can't do anything
ever well once we know Cherokee
then I'm sure
with a very smart grandma that you
that's going to be involved here that
she can say
she can set a schedule
that everybody's going to be happy with
all right
when it comes to nine month old Jonathan
Austin
you are not
[Applause]
[Music]
father is we'll be glad to help you
uh charity you've been great
well thank you very much
Austin
you have learned a lesson
like no other 15 year old I know of
and I'm telling you son
you better carry this lesson with you
until you become a big adult all right
everyone this is Samantha welcome
Samantha
two pieces
who Samantha thought she could trust the
most was her boyfriend Kaelyn
and her sister Tanisha
[Applause]
well you
I guess you're already trying to figure
it out because that trust ended the day
that she found them cuddling on the
couch
[Applause]
and Tanisha was only wearing her
nightgown
and to make it make matters worse
tanisha's 19 years old and the boyfriend
Kalyn is 34.
so Samantha fears at this one incident
may be a symptom of a larger cheating
sex addiction watch there's no limit to
the love that I have for my boyfriend
Caitlin we've been together for two
years and I believe that he's been
cheating on me the main person that I
think Caitlyn has been sleeping around
with is my 19 year old sister Tanisha I
have raised her and affected the fact
that she would do this to me is
unthinkable
one time I called Tanisha and Kailyn
sleeping together on my couch she had
her nightgown on and no bra and I think
Caitlyn is sleeping with other women too
he called me another woman's name while
we were having sex Tanisha and Kailyn
have turned my family apart and I hope
for both of their sake that this is not
true
so
Samantha tell me what happened when you
walked in they were on the couch I woke
up installed Kailyn and Tanisha on the
couch together
and she had on a nightgown with no bra
and I even see her
I asked him why were they sleeping on
the couch together and hear what they
say well they told me they just fell
asleep you also think he might be doing
it with other women too while we were
even having sex he called me another
woman's name
[Applause]
I'm worried about your relationship with
your sister Tanisha what's that like now
well um now me and Tanisha we we're not
as close as we used to be you know
because of this yes because of this and
I want to know uh what's really going on
because I can't keep
um we're gonna find out
everybody here's Kalyn Kalin come on out
here's Kalin welcome to Kalyn everybody
[Music]
[Applause]
I work with I don't believe that I'm not
crazy
[Applause]
how would you describe your relationship
with her sister Tanisha that's my like
my little sister
Tanisha this is what she had to say my
sister Samantha's accused me of sleeping
with her boyfriend Caitlyn kailyn's like
a brother to me if I ever need something
he's there for me my sister and I was
best friends and I feel like I lost my
best friend I just want our relationship
to go back the way it used to be it
hurts me so much that she was accusing
me of doing these things she caught us
on the couch together one time but I
never had sex with him everybody here's
Tanisha
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
are you ready for this Samantha yes
we asked you during your relationship
with Samantha have you ever had sex with
any other woman you said no the lie
detector determined that was a lie more
than one woman
[Applause]
we asked you would you rather be in a
relationship with Tanisha
then Samantha
she said no the lie detector determined
you're telling the truth I told you I
told you that
did you have sex with Tanisha the night
Samantha found the two of you together
on the couch you said no the lie
detector determined you're telling the
truth
[Applause]
[Music]
Samantha have you ever had sex with her
sister Tanisha that says everything
Samantha you said no the lie detector
determined you're telling the truth
you got me way out here for that and I
told you man
man
[Applause]
by the way Samantha just to make this
thing really real we also tested Tanisha
and what she said also means that she
never had anything to do with your voice
[Applause]
I'm sorry what would you thank me out of
our favor man
Samantha
I want you to meet backstage with my
counselor before you go home I want both
of you to see if you can repair your
relationship all right yes we'll be back
everyone this is Brandy welcome Brandon
now
you know I'm a lot of kids in college
watch the show and we know that young
love blossoms on college campuses and
for Brandy while education was her
priority her classmate Marshawn became
her one true love
three years later these two are going
strong and raising their two-year-old
son Dayton together
how's that but
deep within Brandy
is a secret
and it's a secret that she feels that
Marshawn has to hear today no matter how
much it's going to break his heart watch
and Marshawn and I met in college
Marshawn is the only boyfriend that I've
ever had it's not just Marshawn that
means so much to me it's marshawn's
family as well I couldn't have asked for
better people and I want them to know
that I love Marshawn very very much and
I would never intentionally do anything
to hurt him
I'm scared that he's gonna leave me of
course and then he's not gonna be around
dating anymore because Dayton loves his
dad
now I want to remind everybody that
marshawn's backstage but he's secluded
cannot hear or see what's going on here
your first serious boyfriend ever
[Music]
what's the secret when we first started
dating we we used to party a lot and
one night
I had hooked up with someone else when
we first started dating
and
it was his brother
[Applause]
that's his brother D and D has been
keeping this secret too yes and here's
the problem it could be his child right
[Applause]
this is a secret
so he doesn't know
so we we're not swabbing him we can't
give him a DNA test but we did give d a
DNA test
so we will know
if it's these babies and I'm just
trusting you that if it's not D's it has
to be martial right absolutely because
you weren't with no no one else I'm
gonna bring Marshawn out
does he know that D's here
no
here's Marshawn everybody
I told Brandy that you told my producers
it was love at first sight yes it was
first sight soon as I seen her tried to
talk to her at college and she didn't
want to talk to you
but I got it
only that you that you've got a great
child I understand yes he's two years
old wonderful I never thought I liked
being a father but I like it I like it
but she has a secret to tell you
and uh
she feels that she has to tell you now
because she has to get it off her chest
no matter what
you think afterwards but she has to tell
you so tell him I love you
first started
we were partying one drinking a lot
in the night after after your graduation
so
you know I got pregnant with Dayton
immediately and
I slept with somebody else
[Music]
come on brother
are you serious it happened one time but
she's not finished telling you something
[Music]
come here
oh my God I'm done
Marshawn we can we can prove it right
now
we can prove it right now
we can get the truth out right now I'm
sorry baby
Marshawn
we gave
a DNA test a d
and to Dayton
and to Brandy
so we're going to find out right now you
want to find out not now but right now
right now
Marshawn
your brother is here I'd like to bring
him out is that okay
here's d d come on out
[Music]
he wants to apologize that's why he's
here isn't that right Dee yeah yeah I
mean you know you got a long time man we
don't have nothing else it just had one
time
why it was give me one good reason why
it ain't no good reason it was back in
college there was a lot of that got to
do with it I don't know I don't know
what college kids do
yeah
Marshawn you're gonna have a lot of time
to think about this I'm sure you're
going to have a much clearer head than
you have right now and everybody cannot
understand how upset you are all right
let's find out
when it comes to two-year-old Dayton d
you are not the problem
and I know
Marshawn I know there's a lot of healing
to do
and there's a lot of forgiveness to be
given so I want all three of you to see
my counselor Steve before you go home I
want you all to give yourselves a chance
as a family or not a family but make
sure that you think clearly on this okay
we'll be back
everybody this is Tanya welcome Tanya to
the show
now
Tanya admits she made a mistake over six
years ago
she says she's been paying for it ever
since
around the time that she and her
boyfriend Ronnie first began dating
Tanya claims she cheated one time
and although she thought Ronnie had
forgiven her apparently
he never did forgive her why for seven
years I have loved and devoted my life
to Ronnie but right now my heart is
broken because he doesn't think my
four-year-old everyone and my
two-year-old person is his I admit in
the beginning I cheated on Ronnie but it
only happened once and that was three
years before our first daughter was born
he paid more attention to Perseus than
he does to Emerald and it hurts because
she'll come over there and tell me why
doesn't daddy want to spend time with me
or does he love me
right now there's no family and I can't
take it anywhere I want my kids to be
happy and have their dad in their life
you all are together right yes
so he's in the house all the time with
those kids we don't live together right
now oh but you're together oh because of
that did he move out no I did because
[Applause]
and this whole thing about you all being
apart it's all about these kids if it
wasn't for that you'd be together
all right let's meet Ronnie get his take
on this here's wrong
you love her yeah love
you're not living together nope
oh yeah will you admit that you kind of
grinding her all the time about these
kids yep
why do you do that is he cheated on me
that was three two years before she got
cheated on me is the point she cheated
on him can you not get over the fact she
cheated on you nope I made a mistake and
I told her about it there are two
children involved here Ronnie you love
those kids yeah I love those kids it
didn't act like it if you find out that
they're yours you're gonna obvious
you're gonna be a good father today
right huh does that mean that that you
all are going to get back together yeah
you know there comes a time when some
children you know favor one parent and
not the other I mean they don't have to
look Mexican to be your children but you
don't look nothing like me well we're
going to find out right now how's that
in the case of two-year-old Perseus
Ronnie you are the father
and in the case of four-year-old Emerald
[Applause]
thank you